No goats. No glory.
The Men Who Stare at Goats is a comedy, war film directed by Grant Heslov.
A reporter in Iraq might just have the story of a lifetime when he meets Lyn
Cassady, a guy who claims to be a former member of the U.S.
Army's New Earth Army, a unit that employs paranormal powers in their missions.
Lyn Cassady, played by George Clooney.
Bob Wilton, played by Ewan McGregor.
Bill Django, played by Jeff Bridges.
Larry Hooper, played by Kevin Spacey.
Todd Nixon, played by Robert Patrick.
Brigadier General Dean Hopgood, played by Stephen Lang.
The Men Who Stare at Goats is a 2009 satirical black comedy war film
directed by Grant Heslov and written by Peter Straughan.
It is loosely based on the 2004 book by Jon Ronson, about
an investigation into attempts by the U.S.
military to employ psychic powers as a weapon.
The film stars George Clooney, Ewan McGregor, Jeff Bridges, and Kevin Spacey.
The Men Who Stare at Goats premiered at the 66th Venice International Film Festival on September 8,
2009, and was released in the United States and the United Kingdom on November 6.
The film received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of vietnam veteran, kuwait, new
age, paranoid fantasy, hippie lifestyle.
The tone is lighthearted.